I don't wanna be a ninja.
I wanna be a cat burglar.
- Fine. I'll be a ninja, you be a cat burglar.
- No, we both have to be the same thing.
(Raj:)Okay, we're ninjas.
(Leonard:)Thank you.
(Raj:)But next time we'll be cat burglars.
- It's locked.
- Are you sure?
(Howard:)Yes, I'm sure.
(Howard:)Now, you stand guard, I'm...
(Howard:)It's locked.
(Howard:)Just keep an eye out.
I'll have this open in a minute.
(Raj:)When did you learn how to pick locks?
(Howard:)When I was starting to do magic
in junior high...
(Howard:)...I thought I could be an escape artist
like Harry Houdini.
- How did that work out?
- Pretty good.
(Howard:)I managed to escape friends, popularity,
and every party thrown in a 12-mile radius.
(Howard:)- There. Ready?
- Hold on, hold on.